(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T08:22:08.498399",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Welcome to the Fun Zone,
located in God knows where,
we present to you a place where all your wildest dreams can become your reality.
A place where you make the rules.
You can be anyone, you can do anything.
A theme park made to accommodate just you.
We have state-of-the-art rides, food, and entertainment for all of our guests, you'll never want to leave.
So come on down to the Fun Zone,
for the fun has only just begun.
What's up everyone?
It's Bae from— I can't feel my head, oh my god!
みんなようこそさ... 3Dをひと目！
Welcome everyone... take a look at my 3D!
What's up everyone? It's me!
Hello, hello, I see you all! Oh my god, hello!
It's Bae from Hololive English!
Welcome to my 3D showcase!
Hello, hello! There's so many of you! Hello!
Yes! Welcome to the Fun Zone! Welcome to my cage! Isn't my cage brilliant?
It's more of like a summer, som- som- like a summer getaway kind of vacation thing.
Look! Do you see me? Look! Ah! Look at this!
What's up? What's up? Hi everyone! What's up? Isn't it so cool?
Ah, I'm already out of breath, it's like only the beginning, but it's fine, I am here and I'm so happy that we finally got here.
Make sure you use the hashtag— Yay!
Hashtag #RatIdol3D, I want to see all of your screenshots, all of your comments, and let's get it trending, guys, let's go!
やっぱり本当に... 楽しみにしてたので、はい！どうぞ！ハッシュタグ使ってください！はい！
I was really looking forward to it, so please! Go ahead! Please use the hashtag!
De! Well, um, speaking of like 3D,
there's a very special friend and I could not have done this without that him-sa, I just wanted to quickly introduce my dearest friend
and the one who's really in charge of everything, Squeakers!
Lord Squeakers has arrived, everybody! Let's go! Kawaii show! Kawaii desu!
Squeaker, Squeakers has joined the party!
Hi everyone, oh my god chat's going so quick, hello!
Yay! I'm not going to yeet, no, I'm going to be nice to Mr. Squeakers today because he's done a lot for me, I'm going to put you right here.
Well, it is obviously mandatory when it comes to 3D.
We have so much planned today, literally I'm on a time—
I'm on a really big time limit, okay? So you have one minute!
Everyone, you have one minute to give me all the poses that you want me to do, I'm going to do as much as I can, I'm going to read them on the chat!
You have one minute, ready? Time starts now!
I'm waiting! The time is ticking! Jojo-jo! Hai!
Next! Splits, do splits!
I don't know how far I can go. This is as far as I can...
あ！土下座！
Ah, dogeza!
Next!
ナルト走！
Naruto run!
土下座！ I already did the dogeza. And next!
Dogeza! I already did the dogeza. And next!
正座ポーズ
Seiza pose!
マーメイドポーズ
Mermaid pose!
アイリスポーズ
Iris pose!
What is she did?
What is she doing?
クラスファイブ・ハリケーン！
Class-5 hurricane!
Next! You have 10 seconds!
The worm! I'm going to break my entire body, and the show's going to be canceled if I do the worm.
Cartwheel, please! You got a dab? Dab. There we go.
Anyway,
thank you that zoom in. I hope you guys are satisfied with that. I tried my best. Thank you, A-chan, thank you.
Thank you for zooming in. I hope you guys are satisfied with that. I tried my best. Thank you, A-chan, thank you.
All right. Today we have so many things prepared. I've got a lot of songs,
maybe some dances, and I've got a game.
My brain kind of... I had... I've had so much caffeine, guys, my brain is like not working.
We have a game, and I hope you're ready to have some fun.
But for a game, I need people to play games with, because, unless, you know, as you can see, I'm kind of alone here
in my cage, so I really need some friends to play with.
So, I'm going to... Oh, what's that? Wait, what?
I think some people are entering the gates of the Fun Zone. What? Guests? Who could they be? I wonder. なんか来た！方いらっしゃるんじゃないですか？
I think some people are entering the gates of the Fun Zone. What? Guests? Who could they be? I wonder. Oh, someone's here! Could they be coming in?
だめだめの！ You ready to find out? Let's go!
No, no, no! You ready to find out? Let's go!
Yay! Yay!
ゲストが来て！ま、ま、ま、自己紹介お願いします！ Please introduce yourself!
Our guests are here! M-m-m-please introduce yourselves!
最初は… Hi! 皆さん、こんにちは、ハローエブリワン！
First is... Hi! Hello everyone!
I'm a hololive JP member Tokino Sora! 時のそらです！
I'm a hololive JP member, Tokino Sora!
よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いしまーす！
Nice to meet you! Thank you so much!
Hi, everyone! こんこんきつね！ Hololive Fox, Shirakami Fubuki desu. Hi, friends!
Hi everyone! Konkon kitsune! Hololive fox, Shirakami Fubuki here. Hi, friends!
よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
Hi! My name is Oozora Subaru. I'm belong to hololive second generation!
Hi! My name is Oozora Subaru. I belong to hololive 2nd generation!
Today, I'm a rabbit! Yay!
よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
Welcome to the Fun Zone!
FUN ZONE！来てくれて…来てくれて、ねえ、来てくれてありがとう！
Fun Zone! Thank you so much for coming!
なんか、すごいね、ここね！そうですよね！すごい！
It's amazing here, right? It really is! Amazing!
えへへ。まあ、3Dのお祝いとしてね、あの、やっぱりゲームを用意しました！
Hehe. Well, to celebrate the 3D, um, I prepared a game!
I prepared a board game to celebrate, you know, 3D, and so that I can have fun with my precious senpais. So, we're going to play a game together.
これね、私たち… We have game pieces! Everyone has a mascot. They'll be driving along the board in their own go-kart.
So, we... We have game pieces! Everyone has a mascot. They'll be driving along the board in their own go-kart.
マスコット、マスコット！ね、かわいい！ So, for the game, I'm going to explain the rules first.
Mascots, mascots! Aren't they cute? So, for the game, I'm going to explain the rules first.
Ok! We have a dice… お、きた！きた！すっごい！でかい！すっごい！
Okay! We have a dice... Oh, it's here! It's here! It's so big! So huge!
でっかいやん！Big, big! わあ、すごい！てきない！Big, big, die!
It's huge! Big, big! Wow, amazing! Big, big die!
We'll be rolling… そうだよね！ Big dice! Big dice! Big dice!
We'll be rolling... That's right! Big dice! Big dice! Big dice!
So, we'll be rolling this dice...
to advance towards the finish line while we collect cheese.
You can collect cheese by playing minigames or completing a lap.
And when the game is over, the player with the most cheese is the winner!
And when the game is over, the player with the most cheese wins!
え、ピザ！？そら、話聞いてません！
Eh, pizza?! Sora, you're not listening!
And whoever has the fewest pieces of cheese...
has to do a punishment game!
So we have four different spaces that you can land on.
The first space is called a Battle Space.
If you land on this space, you have to compete with other players in a battle game!
The second kind of space is a Baelz Challenge Space!
If you land on this space, you'll be competing against me.
The winner gains 2 cheese, the loser loses 2 cheese!
The third space is a Cheese Space! Very simple.
Land on green to gain cheese, red to lose cheese!
And the last and most interesting space... is a Chaos Space!
Various chaotic things will happen.
So, order! We have to decide the order.
First is Sora-senpai, second is Subaru-senpai, and last is me!
Time to play Rat Trap!
先輩、どうするんですか？塗って始まりましたね。
Senpai, what are we gonna do?
さあ、スタート！スタート！レッツゴー！
Now, start! Start! Let's go!
Battle Space!
The first minigame is Pose and a Phrase!
Challenge the next player with a pose and a one-liner!
Select a topic from these: cool, cute, sexy, angry...
お題どれにする？クール、キュート...セクシー、アングリー。
What topic should we choose?
セクシー！セクシー！セクシー！
Sexy! Sexy!
じゃあ、セクシー対決！セクシー、セクシー、レッツゴー！
Then, a sexy showdown!
え、言葉も？セリフも！？セリフもだよ、そらちゃん！
Eh, words too? Lines too?!
セリフとポーズだよ、そらちゃん！行けるのかい？
Lines and a pose, Sora-chan!
それでは、スリー、ツー、ワン、スタート！
Now then, three, two, one, start!
君、一緒に遊ばない？
Won't you play with me?
セクシー！セクシーチャレンジ！スリー、ツー...
Sexy! Sexy challenge! Three, two...
セクシー？
Sexy?
今日 Fubuki行っていいかな？
Can Fubuki go sexy today?
セクシー！
Sexy!
どっち？ Which one? Which one is better?
Which one is better?
どっちわ…… ちょっと… この人たち
Which one... wait... these people...
ちょっとリトルシャイ？
A little shy?
ああ、シャイすぎた！
Ah, too shy!
そう、キュートだったんだ！
That's right, she was cute!
そうか、キュートだったか。
I see, she was cute.
Yay!
なるほど。
I see.
OK、next.
Okay, next.
いくか！
Let's go!
よし、チーズマスに止まりたい！
Alright, I want to land on the cheese space!
カモンチーズ！
Come on, cheese!
6！ ノーチーズ、ノーチーズ、6！
6! No cheese, no cheese, 6!
セクシー6！
Sexy 6!
いけいけ！ナンバー！ゴー、フブロー！
Go go! Number! Go, Fubulow!
フブローでけえ！
Fubulow is huge!
雷大丈夫か？すごい！
Is the lightning okay? Amazing!
どこまで行くの？
Where is it going?
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
どこまで行くの？
How far does it go?!
止まった、ここか！
It stopped, right here!
ナイススペース！
Nice space!
カモンチーズ！ チーズスペース！
Come on cheese! Cheese Space!
レッド or ブルー、どっち？
Red or blue, which one?
どっちなんだ？
Which one is it?
どっちですか？ レッド？
Which one? Red?
これはレッド！ あー！ ブルー！
This is red! Ah—! Blue!
青色チーズ！ 1チーズ獲得！
Blue cheese! Got 1 cheese!
やったー！ やったー！
Yay! Yay!
OK、next! I get! 6スポット！
Okay, next! I get! 6 spots!
カオス、カオス！
Chaos, chaos!
カオス！ カオス！
Chaos! Chaos!
2！2！2！ カオス！カオス！
2! 2! 2! Chaos! Chaos!
カオス！ ワイワイカオス！ カオス！
Chaos! Wai-wai chaos! Chaos!
カオス！ カオス！ カオス！
Chaos! Chaos! Chaos!
次どなたですか？ 何ですか？
Who is next? What is it?
Baelz Challenge Space!
バトル、バトル、バトル！ フリースタイルダンス！
Battle, battle, battle! Freestyle dance!
フリースタイルダンス？ ちょっと待ってよ！
Freestyle dance? Hold on!
ちょっと待てよ！ これ… 楽しそうだけど！
Wait a minute! This... looks fun though!
やばい！ やばい！
No way! No way!
あ、音楽が流れるみたいで！
Ah, looks like music will play!
やばい、やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
じゃあまず音楽をお願いします。
Well then, please start the music.
バカおしゃれじゃん。
Super stylish.
これに合わせて20秒？
20 seconds to match this?
難しすぎる！
Too difficult!
フリースタイルダンス！
Freestyle dance!
フリースタイルダンスね！
やばい！
No way!
いやいや、フリースタイル全然ダメでしょ！
No way, freestyle is totally no good!
マジでフリースタイルできない！
I really can't freestyle!
じゃあ、これはでも一緒に踊るんじゃない？
Well, shouldn't we dance together for this?
一緒に踊って、じゃあ…そういうやつでしょ？
Dance together, then... that kind of thing, right?
個別！ 個別！ 別々だから！
Individual! Individual! Because they're separate!
別々だから！
Because they're separate!
白上、と空ちゃんがどっちのダンスが魅力的だったか！
Fubuki and Sora-chan will decide whose dance was more appealing!
じゃあ行きます！ 音楽お願いします！
Alright, let's go! Music, please!
始まって… あ、でも！
It started... ah, but!
あ、二人が続けるのか？
Ah, the two of them keep going?
正面も向いてありだよ！
Facing front is also allowed!
二人で一緒にやろうよ！
Let's do it together!
最後ポーズ！
Final pose!
これはちょっと難しいチャレンジだよね。
This is a bit of a difficult challenge.
そうですよね！
That's right!
空ちゃん、どうだったこれ？ 一緒に踊っちゃってるんだよね。
Sora-chan, how was this? You were dancing along.
二人とも負けなしということで！
Both of you didn't lose!
ねえ、空ちゃんこれチーズまた戻ってない？
Hey, Sora-chan, didn't this cheese go back?
泥だ！ 泥だね！
Mud! It's mud!
マイナス2チーズ！ マイナス2！
Minus 2 cheese! Minus 2!
ハーフコース、ルーズ！ 僕らせいじゃないよ！
Half course, loose! It's not our fault!
あたしたのしかったのに！ チーズの借金ですか？
Even though we had fun! Is this cheese debt?
マイナスチーズ！ マイナスチーズ借金！
Minus cheese! Minus cheese debt!
はい、じゃあ僕ですね。
Alright, then it's me.
マイナスチーズ、まさかのマイナス！ マイナススペ…？
Minus cheese, unexpected minus! Minus spe...?
マイナスチーズ！
Minus cheese!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
5！ 5！ みんな違うマスに止まってる。
5! 5! Everyone landed on different spaces.
やいやいやいやいや、ちょっと待って！
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
ちょ、待てないけど！
Wait, I can't wait!
I'm scared!
なにわの
Naniwa's...
Chaos Space!
Hamster wheel!
次の人のターンが終わるまでランニングホイールで走り続ける！
You must keep running on the running wheel until the next person's turn ends!
You must keep running on the running wheel, hamster wheel!
Excuse me! This is my 3D debut stream, you know, kiddo!
ちょっと待て！ねえ、スタッフさん！
Hold on! Hey, staff!
Don't worry!
スー先輩愛してる！
Suu-senpai, I love you!
行きます！スタート！
Here we go! Start!
We have a many times!
We have it many times!
スーパー先輩、アイラブユー、プリーズ！
Super-senpai, I love you, please!
Five!
Cheese Space!
チーズ！
Cheese!
レット・ワ・ブルー！
Blue cheese!
Blue cheese! 1 cheese won!
1 cheese won!
うそキッド！レジェンドチーズ！
No way! Legendary cheese!
降りておいで！降りておいで！ストップ！ストップ！
Come on down! Come on down! Stop, stop!
バコズ、インタビュータイム！インタビュータイム！
Bacos, interview time! Interview time!
What's your feeling?
ナム…ナム…
Rest in peace...
じゃあ次！次、ナイスファイト！行くぞ！
Okay, next! Next, nice fight! Let's go!
Battle Space!
Charades! ジェチャゲーム！OK！
Charades! Charades game! Okay!
他3人がジェスチャーを当てる、制限時間30秒以内に3つ出来たらクリア！
The other three guess the gestures. Clear if you get 3 within 30 seconds!
うまい！いけるんじゃないか？
Nice! Can we do this?
3つ連続？あ、じゃあ3つ？
Three in a row? Ah, three then?
よーい、スタート！
Ready, start!
コアラ！
Koala!
マッスル！ボディビルディング！
Muscle! Bodybuilding!
プッシュ！ピー！
Flush? Pee?
トイレに行く！
Going to the restroom!
やった！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
マイターン！マイターン！
My turn! My turn!
Two!
Chaos Space!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
カオスやべえよマジで。
This chaos is insane, seriously.
カオスの内容は？
What's the content of the chaos?
おっ！
Oh!
ベジマイトを食べないと前に進むことができない
You cannot advance any further until you eat Vegemite.
すばる先輩ベジマイト大好き！やったー！ベジマイト！
Subaru-senpai loves Vegemite! Yay! Vegemite!
ベジマイトっていうことで、ベジマイト大好き？
Does that mean you love Vegemite?
アイラブベジマイト。
I love Vegemite.
いたかいのりで匂いを嗅いで
Smell it first.
なんか、二人ともまだ食べたことないんで
Wait, neither of us has ever eaten it before.
テイスティ！
Tasty!
匂いだけだと
Just by the smell...
味は味噌？
Tastes like miso?
味噌？
Miso?
いつぶりだろ？ベジマイト。
It's been a while since I last had Vegemite.
久しぶりのベジマイトをどうぞ。
Go ahead, enjoy your fresh Vegemite.
いただきます。
Itadakimasu.
待って待って待って待って！私もち、ベジマイト食べたい！
Wait, wait, wait, wait! I want to eat Vegemite too!
テイスティ！
Tasty!
美味しい？
Delicious?
給食の味！
Tastes like school lunch!
休憩、休憩フードみたいな
Like a snack/break food.
いいなー！ベジマイト食べてみたい！
Aw, man! I want to try Vegemite!
味噌汁だ！味噌汁！ライフは味噌スープ！よねみんぐ、味噌スープ、にょにょにょにょにょにょ
Miso soup! Miso soup! Life is miso soup!
の、飲んでる方が結構カオス感あったぞ。
Drinking it actually felt more chaotic.
じゃあ次は
Alright, next is...
サイコロ行きます！
Rolling the die!
はい！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ファイブ！
Five!
さあ次は？
So, next is...
何のマスになるかな？
What space will we land on?
戻れる！
We're going back!
さあ、こちらのマスは？
Now, what is this space?
なんのマスでしょうか？
What space could it be?
カオススペース！ジャジャジャジャーン！
Chaos Space! Ta-da!
カオスの内容は？
What's the content of the chaos?
ちょっと待って！
Wait a second!
ハプニングウェーブ、スタート位置に戻る
Surprise Warp: Return to the start.
チーズが２つ減る
Lose 2 cheese.
待って？
Wait?
グッバイハカーズ！
Goodbye, Hakars!
投石機じゃねえか！
That's a catapult!
ちょっと待て！ちょっと待て！ちょっと待て！
Wait a second! Wait a second! Wait a second!
グッバイハカーズ！
Goodbye, Hakars!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ハカーズ！
Hakars!
マイナス２ということは？
Minus 2 means...?
あいみんマイナス？
Aimin minus?
元々マイナス２意味だから、マイナス４？
Since it's originally minus 2, that's minus 4?
あ、でもマイナス４チーズ。
Ah, but minus 4 cheese.
頑張って。頑張れしょ。頑張れしょ。頑張れしょ。頑張れ！
Do your best. You can do it.
マイナス、結構ゲットしてるぞ。
You're getting quite a few minuses.
マイナス３！マイナス３！
Minus 3! Minus 3!
じゃあ続いて、そらちゃん。
Alright, next is Sora-chan.
最悪。
The worst.
チーズ食べれないね。
Can't eat cheese.
チーズ食べようよ。
Let's eat cheese.
チーズ欲しい！アイウォントチーズ！
I want cheese! I want cheese!
レッツゴー！レッツゴー！レッツゴー！
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
どうかな？ファイブ！ファイブ！
How is it? Five! Five!
ホーが一杯出るね。
Lots of 'Ho's coming out.
ファイブゴー！ファイブゴー！ファイブゴー！
Five go! Five go! Five go!
ファイブゴー！ファイブゴー！ファインダー！
Five go! Five go! Finder!
あれ？あれ？おっと！チーズゲット！ゴール！
Huh? Huh? Oh! Cheese get! Goal!
チーズゲット！ナイスー！
Cheese get! Nice!
一周したらですね、チーズゲットということで、このマス（チーズもらえるってことで）
Once you make a full lap, you get cheese, so this space...
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
おめでとう！セレブレーション！
Congratulations! Celebration!
バトルスペース！
Battle Space!
バトル？
Battle?
Whats the battle this time?
ポーズ＆フレーズ
Pose and a Phrase
なるほど！
I see!
お題はこの中から選べる 【かっこいい/可愛い/セクシー/怒る/自由】
Select a topic from these [cool/cute/sexy/angry/free].
まだ、まだ一緒？
Still, still together?
アイ　ウォント　トゥー　ルック　ベリーベリー　アングリーソラ！
I want to look very, very angry Sora!
アングリーソラ！アングリーソラ先輩！アングリーソラ先輩！
Angry Sora! Angry Sora-senpai! Angry Sora-senpai!
セリフもあるね。
There's a line too.
一言、一言言って。
Say a line, a one-liner.
アングリーソラ！よし。
Angry Sora! Alright.
アングリーソラ、３、２、１、ゴー！
Angry Sora, 3, 2, 1, go!
本当にムカつく！もうあんたは敵なんだから！
I am seriously pissed off! You're my enemy now!
怖い！怖い！怖い！拍手、拍手、拍手！スケアリー！
Scary! Scary! Scary! Clap, clap, clap! Scary!
ナイスパフォーマンス！
Nice performance!
アイ　アム　ユア　フレンド！
I am your friend!
次は、フーブキー！
Next is Fubuki!
フーブキー！おこう！３、２、１、ゴー！
Fubuki! Okou! 3, 2, 1, go!
あのさ、請求書のこれ１０万円って何？
Hey, what is this 100,000 yen on the invoice?
何のガチャ引いたの？良くないよ、そういうのはさ。
What gacha did you pull? That's not good, you know.
白髪のオネショしたいって言ったよね？
You said you wanted to wet the sheets like Shirakami, right?
なんて言ったの？待って待って！
What did you say? Wait, wait!
キャラ設定大丈夫？大丈夫？大丈夫？
Is your character setting okay? Is it okay? Is it okay?
マジマジ。キャラ設定入りすぎて
Seriously, you're getting way too into character.
シズカな怒りだって
It's quiet anger, they said.
確かにね。
True, true.
ちょっと難しかったわ。
That was a bit difficult.
そうだよ。難しかった。
Yeah, it was hard.
厳しいね。
Tough, huh.
ソリソリ。
Sorry, sorry.
ちょっと、こっちからこうという
Wait, coming from this side like...
やった！ウィー！
Yay, I did it! Woo!
本物の本物のキツネだった！
That was the fox!
that was actually really smooth.
Real smooth, Fubuki.
やったー！じゃあ一番進める！
Yay! Let's go first!
で、これでチーズはスブちゃんゲットした！
And with this, Fubuki gets the cheese!
やったー！やったー！
Yay!
よし、じゃあ。
Alright then.
じゃあ次かな？
So, who's next?
はーい！やったー！
Yay!
白髪鬼で最後？もしや。
Is this the last one, maybe?
おっ！これで最後かな？
Oh! Is this the last one?
で、最後って書いてます！
It says "last"!
ツー！ツー！ツー！
Two? Two?
ツーはなんだ？ナイス！ナイス！ナイス！
What is two? Nice!
What's it gonna be?
何来る？
What will it be?
バトルスペース！ナイス！ナイス！
Battle Space! Nice!
うわ、バトル！
Whoa, battle!
What kind of battle?
なんだ？
What's this?
早口言葉！
Tongue Twisters!
負ける！
You're gonna lose!
No!
早口言葉！次振る人と勝負。
It's the Tongue Twisters.
先に噛んだほうが負け。
Yay, let's do this!
やった！早口言葉でいきましょう！
Yay!
よし、スパーク！It's over! It's over! It's over!
It's over! It's over! It's over!
これもう終わりです。
This is the end, you know.
え、チーズ一個！
One more cheese!
I will be you!
あはは！
Uh-huh.
やばい、やばい、やばい。
Yikes, yikes!
やばい、やばい。
一体何の早口言葉になるかな？
What kind of tongue twister will it be?
はい、OK。
Okay.
もういっかい、What's it gonna be?
Come on!
神アニメハコス大興奮！
Kamianime hakos daikouhun!
なるほど、OK。
I see. Okay.
3パーセント！大丈夫ですか？
Is everyone okay?
じゃあ白髪からいきますか？
Shall we start from the white-haired one?
Three times、3回言うんですよね？
You have to say it three times, right?
OK、3回。
Okay, three times.
はい、Ready? Go!
Ready? Go!
神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮！
Kamianime hakos daikouhun!
うおおおお！さすがさすが！
As expected!
イエイ、そうそう。すごっ！
That's right!
OK！
Nice!
次私？
Next is me!
OK、Ready?
Okay, ready?
OK。
Okay.
すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮！
Kamianime hakos daikouhun!
うおお！すごい！すごい！
Woo!
じゃあ、次がありますからね。
Who's next?
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな！
Nakanaka katakana kakenakattana!
いや、これはイケるしょ。
This one is doable, though.
おー、自信がありますね。
Oh, you're confident!
ありますよ。じゃあ次いきましょうか。
Let's go.
すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな！
Nakanaka katakana kakenakattana!
これはすごい！すごい！すごーい！
This is amazing! Amazing!
ふぶきちゃってロボットなんだ。
Fubuki-chan is a robot, right?
No, robot!
No robot!
Next！
Next!
すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな！
Nakanaka katakana kakenakattana!
おっ！おっ？
Oh! Oh!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
すごい！すごい！これは...
This is...
トピック3、やばいぞ、これ。
Topic 3, this is yikes!
やばいぞ、これ！
This is yikes!
I wonder who's gonna be...
あのときのときのそら！
Anotokino tokinosora!
なるほど！
I see, I see.
あのときのときのそらね、はいはい。
Anotokino tokinosora.
ちょっと難しそうだな。
It's a bit difficult.
OK、OK、OK。
Okay, okay, okay.
すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら！
Anotokino tokinosora!
これ、かわいいじゃん！
That was cute!
かわいい！
So cute!
これさ、結構難しくない？たぶん。
Is it difficult to say?
どうぞ、どうぞ。
Go ahead, go ahead.
OK、次、すばる先輩、3、2:1、Go!
Okay, next, Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら！
Anotokino tokinosora!
うおおお！
Whoa!
これ、やばいな。
This is yikes!
やばいな、意外と。
Yikes, surprisingly...
全然負けないぞ！
We're not losing at all!
ちょっともっと難しいやつ出てこいよ！
Let's bring out a more difficult one!
一番難しいやつ、Come on!
Come on!
あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
あぶりカルビ！あぶりカルビ！
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
そう、あぶりカルビ。難しい！
Is it difficult?
え、本当？本当に？
Really? Really?
あぶ、あぶりカルビ。言ってミー、Try!
Try saying it, try!
あぶりカルビ、あっ、そうか。
Aburi karubi... Oh, right.
OK、次、すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Okay, next, Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
あぶりカルビ！
大丈夫ですか？大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
あぶりカルビでいいんだ、あぶりカルビ、ほら。
Aburi karubi is fine, aburi karubi...
あぶりカルビ！あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
OK、次、すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Okay, next, Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、よっしゃー！
Aburi karubi!
すごい、すごい、すごい！Night of the night 4K！
You got this! You got this!
あー、もう一回連続で！
One more time, consecutively.
Then we're doing one more time, we have to say five times!
And this time, one more time, you have to say it five times!
5回！5回！
Five times!
5 times！5回！
Say it five times!
これがファイナル！
This is the final!
ファイナル！OK、OK。
Final! Okay, okay.
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
OK。
Okay.
OK、すばる先輩、3、2、1、Go!
Okay, Subaru-senpai, three, two, one, go!
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
いや、これさ、早口言葉かったらもう...
This tongue twister battle is like...
あー、そうか！あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ先輩！
Subaru-senpai!
あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ、あぶりカルビ！
Aburi karubi!
ちょっと待って、両方勝ってない？
Wait, did both of them win?
ちょっと待って、待って、待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
罰ゲームです！二人とも罰ゲームです！
It's a punishment! Both of you get punished!
え、でも、こっちも思っちゃった！
Wait, but we thought so too!
私たちこっちです！
We're on this side!
私たちこっちです！えへへ
We're on this side! Ehehe~
すごい！え、待ってよ！手手、手手！
Amazing! Wait, hands, hands!
やあ、手手、手手！ってことは二人とも罰ゲームってことで？
Yeah, hands, hands! That means you both get punished?
ゲームオーバー！あ、違う！
Game over! Ah, wait, no!
いやあ、もうすごい！最後、すごい！
Man, that was amazing! That last part was amazing!
Crazy Battle!
We are going to now announce the winner! 結果発表したいと思います！
We are going to now announce the winner! We will now announce the results!
The player who collected the most pieces of cheese is...
You are a leader! そら先輩もう！た、た、た、た、た！
You are a leader! Sora-senpai too! Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
だーれだ！We have a tie!
Who could it be? We have a tie!
よねえ、ちょっと待って！タイム！ちょっと待って！タイム！
Right? Wait! Time! Wait a second! Time!
The player who collected the fewest pieces of cheese is...
は、罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！
Pu-, punishment! Punishment!
バツゲーム！バツゲーム！バツゲーム！
Penalty game! Penalty game! Penalty game!
バツゲーム！悪いねずみはバツゲームだって！バツゲームだ！
Penalty game! Bad mice get a penalty game! It's a penalty game!
What's a batz game? I don't know what this batz game is.
バツゲーム！トモさん、お願いします！
Penalty game! Tomo-san, please!
わあすー！カモン！
Waasu! Come on!
バイバイ！ゲームオーバー！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Game over! Bye-bye!
え、でもどこいっちゃったんだろう？こわ、こわ、スケスケ、スケスケ、はい、はい、ヘルプミー！
Eh, but where did she go? Scary, scary, see-through, see-through, yes, yes, help me!
ヘルプミー！ヘルプミー！お、なんかおちこお、声がする。
Help me! Help me! Oh, I hear a voice.
ヘルプミー！なんの意味も、何の意味も make any sense.
Help me! It doesn't make any sense at all.
Why am I here? I shouldn't be here.
あら？あ、今日でもね、はこすっちゃんのね、3Dお披露目だったんだけど
Oh? Ah, today was Hakos-chan's 3D reveal debut, but...
このままじゃ動物園に、Let's go! Let's go by us!
At this rate, to the zoo—Let's go! Let's go by us!
泣いちゃった！泣いちゃった！泣いちゃった！泣いちゃった！
She cried! She cried! She cried! She cried!
I present cheese. Yes, cheese.
クレ、チーズを、あの、チ、チ、チ、チーズ、と、と、ないで、ないで！
Give me, cheese... um, gi-, gi-, gi-, cheese, do, don't, don't!
すぶき！の、チーズすぶき！チーズ！チーズ！チーズ、チーズ！
Fubuki! No, cheese Fubuki! Cheese! Cheese! Cheese, cheese!
まあ、ということで、今日みんな来てくれて本当にありがとうございます。こちらは檻の中で、
Well, with that said, thank you so much everyone for coming today. Here inside the cage...
みんなのね、感想を聞きたいんですけど、ベリーベリーサッドしちゃった？そらちゃんから今日のどうでしたか？
We'd love to hear everyone's thoughts, but she got very, very sad. Sora-chan, how was today?
Yeah, well, how do you feel?
Yeah, I'm so very excited. Excited game and... uh, me-, many... ah, asobeta, many playing game... ah, so, happy! Yeah!
Yeah, I'm so very excited. Excited game and... um, ma-, many... ah, we got to play, many playing games... ah, so happy! Yeah!
Congratulations! 3Dオメデトウ！3Dオメデトウ！
Congratulations! Happy 3D! Happy 3D!
おめでとう！3Dお披露目おめでとう！楽しかったね！ありがとうございます！
Congratulations! Congratulations on your 3D reveal! It was so much fun! Thank you very much!
あ、それと、こよちゃんのラボに送ろう？あ、そう！こよラボに！実験マウス！実験マウス！Please, no! Stop! まあまあまあまあ！
Oh, and should we send her to Koyori's lab? Ah, yeah! To Koyori Lab! Test mouse! Test mouse! Please, no! Stop! Well, well, well, well!
はい、次すばちゃん。見て見て！I'm very happy because today Hakosuzu 3D showcase! Yeah!
Next, Subaru-chan. Look, look! I'm very happy because today is Hakosuzu's 3D showcase! Yeah!
3Dショーケース！3Dショーケース！これ、ケース！ケース！これが、これが、これが、これがお披露目だったのか。そう！楽しかった。だよね。
3D showcase! 3D showcase! This, case! Case! So this, this, this, this was the reveal. That's right! It was fun. Right.
Thank you so much for coming. すんでくれて、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming. Thank you for living here!
ちょっと、これからも一応ライブするので、はい！ダンスも、このまま、ここ、ここで、ここで、ここで、ここで、なんのこと！
We'll be doing lives from now on, so yes! Dancing too, right here, right here, right here, what are you talking about!
The next one, the next Hakos will have some songs I'm going to sing and I'm going to perform, so I hope everyone please continue watching me. まだまだ盛り上がっていきましょう！これから出る、出ます、これから、頑張って！
The next one, the next Hakos will have some songs I'm going to sing and I'm going to perform, so I hope everyone please continue watching me. Let's keep getting more and more hyped! There's more coming out, coming out, from now on, do your best!
頑張って！頑張って！お疲れ様！ Thank you! Oopsie! Enjoy showcase! Enjoy showcase! みんな大好き！
Do your best! Do your best! Good job! Thank you! Oopsie! Enjoy showcase! Enjoy showcase! I love you all!
Baby, how's your life?
Are you living free?
Let's forget everything and have some fun
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice,
here we just play dice!
Baby, baby there's no need to think twice,
Make it your night, make it your fight,
Get out from the hamster wheel and rule your life!
5 4 3 2 1 play dice!
Hey, hey, bae, bae
Baby...
So the space went "bang" and we were all born,
The order we knew, ripped and torn.
But we have no time to complain
'cause life is short, can't do it over again.
If we can laugh, it doesn't matter where or when
Be 自チュー 奔放
Be self-indulgent and free,
Physics don't play the dice?
So let trouble stir and rise!
Be limits, bounds, rules or chains...
意味 なンテ な あ あ い
What do any of them mean anyway?
So we don't give a chu
So we don't give a kiss
ヤ なこと は そっと mute
And mute whatever sucks,
So find something new
身体 中 一瞬 で 夢中 ha！
Getting lost in the moment in a flash!
No cage can trap this rat
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Yell and scream come on now, don't be too nice
Follow your heart, pump your fist up, come and join the club
Go and scream for you the one who’s flying free
Go and scream for you, the one who's flying free,
カオス の ダイス の まま で いい
Letting chaos roll the dice just as it is!
For this moment I am truly really me!
5 4 3 2 1 play dice!
Blah blah blah blah nandra kandra
Blah blah blah blah, whatever,
Blah blah blah blah rati rata rat rat
Blah blah blah blah, ratty rat rat,
Blah blah blah blah nandra kandra
Blah blah blah blah, whatever,
Blah blah blah blah
Blah blah blah blah, ratty rat rat,
Now here I will recite to you
The only thing that will hold true
YOLO is my ninja way
It’s time put those moves out there on display
It's time to put those moves out there on display
Why stress about tomorrow when you’ve got today?
Why stress about tomorrow when you've got today?
Be 余チュー 紐々
Live life to the absolute fullest,
今が最高か最低かなんて誰も知らない
Nobody knows if today's high or low,
人生 鼠 生 チュー
Life is short, live it up as a rat,
生 くて マジ で みじ か あ あ い
Living it is seriously so damn short!
Wow, aren’t we sick as chu?
Wow, aren't we sick as chu?
我々ってエゴい cute
We're so egoistic and cute
So rush on to our route
火花 走らせ まるで 電流 ha!
Sparks flying like an electric current!
No math can settle this rat
(Bae!)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Come and venture into my dope dumpsite
Time to run and follow our sun, won’t stop till we’re done
Time to run and follow our sun, won't stop till we're done
Idiots are allowed infinite fun
みんな自由じゃなくちゃもったいないじゃん
Everyone's got to be free, it'd be a waste otherwise!
It’s never too late, our journey’s just begun!
It's never too late, our journey's just begun!
If you hesitate on what to do,
That’s it, game over. You are screwed.
That's it, game over. You are screwed.
泣いても笑っても chu chu chu
Whether crying or laughing, chu chu chu
Baby, baby, it’s our time! It’s our time!
Baby, baby, it's our time! It's our time!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Chu-chu-chu!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice
Here we just play dice!
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice
Dari-wari, woah
Make it your night, make it your fight
Make it your spotlight
Get out from the hamster wheel and rule your life
Five, four, three, two, one, play dice!
(Hey, hey, bae, bae)
Baby
So the space went "bang" and we were all born
The order we knew, ripped and torn
But we have no time to complain
'Cause life is short, can't do it over again
If we can laugh, it doesn't matter where or when
Be 自チュ奔放
Be free-spirited and wild
Physics don't play the dice?
So let trouble stir and rise
Be limits, bounds, rules, or chains
意味なんかない
Meaninglessly useless
So we don't give a chu
厄介なことはそっとmute
Quietly mute all trouble
So find something new
身体中一瞬で夢中
Lost in the moment all over
No cage can trap this rat
(Bae!)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice
Here we just play dice!
Yell and scream, come on now
Don't be too nice, dari-wari, woah
Follow your heart, pump your fist up
Come and join the club
Go and scream for you, the one who's flying free
カオスのダイスのままでいい
It's fine to stay in the chaos of dice
For this moment I am truly really me
Five, four, three, two, one, play dice!
Blah, blah, blah, blah
Nandra kandra
Rati, rata, rat, rat
Blah, blah, blah, blah
Nandra kandra
Now here I will recite to you
The only thing that will hold true
Yolo is my ninja way
It's time put those moves out there on display
Why stress about tomorrow when you've got today?
Be 余チュ繋々
Be endlessly connected in leisure
今が最高か最低かなんて誰も知らない
Nobody knows if now is the best or worst
人生鼠生チュ生ってマジで短かい
Life as a rat, life of chu, truly so short
Wow, aren't we sick as chu?
我々ってエグいcute
Aren't we fiercely cute?
So rush on to our route
花火走らせまるで電流ha!
Fireworks running like electric currents ha!
No math can settle this rat
(Bae!)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice
Here we just play dice!
Come and venture into my dope dumpsite
Dari-wari, woah
Time to run and follow our sun
Won't stop until we're done
Idiots are allowed infinite fun
みんな自由じゃなきゃもったいないじゃん
It's a waste if everyone isn't free
タイヨウのうた
[Title: Taiyou no Uta]
It's never too late, our journey's just begun
If you hesitate on what to do
That's it, game over, you are screwed
泣いていてもchu-chu-chu
Whether crying or laughing, chu-chu-chu
Baby, baby, it's our time
(It's our time)
Chu-chu-chu
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice
Here we just play dice!
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice
Dari-wari, woah
This is our night, this is our fight
This is our spotlight
Before giving in, go show them your best try
ふうえている 私の 手 に
Trembling in my hands,
後悔しちゃったらもう生ききれない
If you regret it, you can't live it out
初めて 君 が 触れ て
for the first time you touched me,
Whatchu doing bruh, go out and live your life
Five, four, three, two, one, play dice!
Hey, hey, my bae
優しい 気持ち あたたかさに やっと 気づい た ん だ
and I finally realized the tender warmth.
Baby, don't care
閉ざし た 窓 開けれ ば
If I open the closed window,
Hey, hey, my bae
Bae don't be scared
新しい 風 が 吹い た
a new wind will blow.
Hey, hey, my bae
Baby, don't care
笑っ て 泣い て 君 と 出会え て
Smiling, crying, meeting you,
(Now sing baby?)
見える 世界 は 輝き だし た
the world I see began to shine.
Blah, blah, blah, blah
Nandra kandra
ひまわり 揺れる タイヨウ の 下 で
Under the sun where sunflowers sway,
Blah, blah, blah, blah
Rati, rata, rat, rat
感じ て いた 風 を 君 を
I felt the wind and you.
Blah, blah, blah, blah
Nandra kandra
信じる こと 迷う こと も 立ち止まる こと も 全部
Believing, hesitating, and stopping—all of it
Blah, blah, blah, blah
私 が ここ で 生き て いる 答え かも しれ ない
might be the answer that I am living here.
モノクロ の 毎日 が 色づい て ゆく よう に
As days in monochrome begin to gain color,
笑っ て 泣い て 君 と 出会え て 続く 未来 は 輝い て いた
smiling, crying, meeting you, the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり 揺れる タイヨウ の 下 で 私 の まま 明日 を 歌う よ
Under the sun where sunflowers sway, I will sing of tomorrow just as I am.
限り ある 日々 を 止められない 時間 を どれ だけ 愛せる か な ？ 愛せる よ ね
Through limited days and unstoppable time, how much can I love? I can love, right?
君 が いれば 光さえもそらさないで
With you here, I won't look away from even the light.
笑っ て 泣い て 君 と 出会え て
Smiling, crying, meeting you,
続く 未来 は 輝い て いた
the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり 揺れる タイヨウ の 下 で 私 の まま 明日 を …
Under the sun where sunflowers sway, I will sing of tomorrow...
ありがとう 伝え たい 今 なら 言える よ 過ごし た 季節 も 忘れ は し ない よ
I want to thank you, now I can say it, and I won't forget the seasons we spent.
ひまわり 揺れる タイヨウ の よう に 私 の うた 君 を 照らす よ
Like the sun where sunflowers sway, my song will illuminate you.
私 の まま 君 を …
Just as I am, you...
La la la la...
笑っ て 泣い て 君 と 出会え て
Smiling, crying, meeting you,
続く 未来 は 輝い て い た
the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり 揺れる タイヨウ の 下 で 私 の まま …
Under the sun where sunflowers sway, just as I am...
明日 を 歌う よ
I will sing of tomorrow.
限りある日々を 止まらない時間を
Days that are limited, time that doesn't stop,
どれだけ愛せるかな
how much can I love them?
愛せるよね 君がいれば
I can love them if you're here.
光さえも そらさないで
Don't look away, even from the light.
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えて
Smiling, crying, meeting you,
続く未来は 輝いていた
the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり揺れる タイヨウの下で
Under the sun where sunflowers sway,
感じていた風を 君を
I felt the wind, I felt you.
信じること 迷うことも 立ち止まることも全部
Believing, hesitating, and stopping in my tracks—
私が今ここで生きてる 答えかもしれない
maybe all of that is the answer to why I live here now.
モノクロの毎日が 色づいていくように
As if my monochrome days are starting to gain color,
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えて
smiling, crying, meeting you,
続く未来は 輝いていた
the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり揺れる タイヨウの下で
Under the sun where sunflowers sway,
私の明日を歌うよ
I'll sing of my tomorrow.
限りある日々を 止まらない時間を
Days that are limited, time that doesn't stop,
どれだけ愛せるかな
how much can I love them?
愛せるよね 君がいれば
I can love them if you're here.
光さえも そらさないで
Don't look away, even from the light.
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えて
Smiling, crying, meeting you,
続く未来は 輝いていた
the future ahead was shining bright.
ひまわり揺れる タイヨウの下で
Under the sun where sunflowers sway,
私の明日を ありがとう伝えたい 今なら言えるよ
I want to say thank you for my tomorrow; now I can say it.
過ごした季節も 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the seasons we spent together either.
ひまわり揺れる タイヨウのように
Like the sun where sunflowers sway,
私のうた 君を照らすよ
my song will illuminate you.
私のまま 君を 君を…
Just as I am, you, you...
la la la la la la la
Yeah! Thank you so much for listening. That was Taiyou no Uta, y'know?
Um, so, for those who know, um, Taiyou no Uta is a very special song to me...
because that was a, the very first song that I ever learnt, um, very first song that I ever learnt how to play...
because that was, uh, the very first song that I ever learned, um, very first song that I ever learned how to play,
how to sing by myself in a music room.
So I really hope you guys enjoyed it.
We're gonna keep going! Next song is also a very, very, very special and fun song...
that I vowed I would perform one day, so I hope you guys enjoy. Are you ready for the next song?
チャンス×チャンス 逢！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan!
喟呼！！チキチキバンバン
Aa!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
愛！！チュキチュキチュキバンバン
Ai!! Chuki Chuki Chuki Ban Ban!
HIGH チキチキバンバン
HIGH! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan!
猫も杓子も みんな気狂いでツラァァァイ
Cats and masters, everyone's crazy, it's so painful!
酔えばテキーラ あらぬ妄想連続でピカァァーン
Drunk on tequila, continuous wild delusions flash!
夢はパンドラ ほら 開けたくなっ…
Dreams are Pandora, hey, you wanna open them...
みんな期待してパリピアー
Everyone's expecting to be party people,
今夜フジヤマ登らにゃわからなーい
can't understand without climbing Mt. Fuji tonight!
決戦は週末の宿命
The decisive battle is weekend's destiny,
チャンス×チャンス 逢！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back anything, enjoy the fever night!
チャンス×チャンス 哀！？チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai!? Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
何度無茶苦茶したってパリズナイ
No matter how many times we go wild, it's party's night!
チャンス×チャンス 喟呼！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Aa!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
愚か者ほどHIGHと化す完全社会
The more foolish, the higher they get in this total society!
チャンス×チャンス 愛！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's a budding superstar, diva night!
チャンス×チャンス 喟呼！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Aa!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
愚か者ほどHIGHと化す完全社会
The more foolish, the higher they get in this total society!
チャンス×チャンス 愛！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's a budding superstar, diva night!
チャンス×チャンス 逢！！チキチキバンバン
Chance x chance! Ai! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan!
喟呼！！チキチキバンバン
Aa!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
愛！！チュキチュキチュキバンバン
Ai!! Chuki Chuki Chuki Ban Ban!
HIGH チキチキバンバン
HIGH! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan!
喟呼！！チキチキバンバン
Aa!! Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
愛！！チュキチュキチュキ
Ai!! Chuki Chuki Chuki...
チャン×チャン 逢！！チキチキバンバン
Chan x Chan! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
哀！？チキチキ チャン チャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan
嗟呼！ チキチキバンバン
Aa! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
愛！！ チュキチュキチュキ バンバン
Ai!! Chuki Chuki Chuki Bam Bam
high チキチキバンバン
High Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
哀！？チキチキ チャン チャン
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Chan Chan
嗟呼！ チキチキバンバン
Aa! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
愛！！ チュキチュキ
Ai!! Chuki Chuki
猫も杓子も
Even your cats and wooden ladles,
みんな 気まぐれ で 辛い
Everyone is fickle, it's frustrating.
酔え ば テキーラ
If you get drunk on tequila,
有 ら ぬ 妄想 連続 で ピークアン
Your head is full of endless delusions.
夢 は パンドラ ほら 開け たく なる
Dreams are like Pandora's box, making you want to open them.
みんな 期待 し て パリピ よ
Everyone, get excited, party people!
今夜 富士山 昇 ら にゃ 分から ない
You won't know until you climb Mt. Fuji tonight.
決戦 も 週末 の 宿命
The final battle is a weekend destiny.
チャン × チャン
Chan x Chan
逢 ！！ チキチキバンバン
Ai!! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
何 も 勿体 振ら ず 楽しめ fever tonight
Don't hold back and enjoy the fever tonight!
チャン × チャン
Chan x Chan
哀 ！？ チキチキバンバン ！！
Ai!? Chiki Chiki Bam Bam!
何 度 むしゃくしゃ し たって party tonight
No matter how many times you feel frustrated, party tonight!
チャン × チャン
Chan x Chan
嗟呼 ！ チキチキバンバン
Aa! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
オロカモノ ホド high とかす 完全 社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get!
チャン × チャン
Chan x Chan
逢 ！！ チキチキバンバン
Ai!! Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
みんな スーパースター の 卵 さ diva tonight
Everyone is a superstar in the making, diva tonight!
セクシーシークレット
Sexy secret
巻き込むメイク誰いいでしょ？
Wrapped-up makeup, isn't that nice?
燃え盛るカップルケドいいでしょう？
Burning couples, aren't they nice?
もう少しトワイライトもう少しブライト
A little more twilight, a little more bright
熱が来るゲルゲロ危険物どうだい
Heat is coming, dangerous goods, how's that?
ほらほら違いにスポット天乃
Look, look, spotlight on the different heavens
いつまでダウンラー気だ8時間
How long are you acting down, 8 hours?
チャン チャン 愛 チキチキバンバン
Chan Chan Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
愛 チキチキ チャンチャン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chan Chan
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ チキバンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
オー BABY こさくしね はははは
Oh baby, shut the fuck up, ha ha ha
ハイイセツキラ マインタクミタイレイアイデショウ
High-class sparkle, my taxi driver, is that right?
モエサカッチケドイデショウ
Burning up, isn't that nice?
モスクシブライガ モスクシブライヤ
A little more bright, a little more bright
アズカブクルゲロキデアンウエオダイ
Asakawa coming, gelgero, kind of up-down
ホラホラジャガイニスポッタテンナ
Look, look, spot in the potatoes
チャン チャン 愛 チキチキバンバン
Chan Chan Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
愛 チキチキ チャンチャン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chan Chan
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ チキバンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
チャン チャン 愛 チキチキバンバン
Chan Chan Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
愛 チキチキ チャンチャン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chan Chan
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ チキバンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
アイチキチキ バンバン
Ai Chiki Chiki Bam Bam
Ha-! Thank you everyone!
Ha—! Thank you everyone!
That was Chikichikibanban! I'm so glad that I was able to dance the dance as well as sing the song!
I'm just so heavy—! Thank you! Did not really run, did not really run.
Of course we had to do the run. Anyway, thank you so much for listening to my third, and...
...final song! Saigo no kyoku, ano kiite kurete arigatou! Saigo, final!
...final song! Thank you so much for listening to my final song!
Yes, that was totally my final song. But thank you so much for watching everyone!
It is time for the... announcement time! Announcement time!
It is time for... announcement time! Announcement time!
But to help me do this announcement, I need a very special helper. Hi! Helper, please! I need help!
Squeakers, otsukaresama! Otsukaresama desu! Otsukaresama, you're doing great.
Squeakers, good job! Great job! You're doing great, Squeakers!
Lord Squeakers, you're doing great. Thank you, Lord Squeakers! I present to you the Street Rat T-shirt!
Yes, this is my official 3D stream merch! And yes, I have very little time to show this, so we're going to... we're on the clock, okay?
Yes, this is my official 3D stream merch! And I have very little time to show this, so we're on the clock, okay?
Okay, how fast can I do the showcase? Here we go! There are six key features of this T-shirt. Six! Okay, let me sell it to you.
Okay, how fast can I do the showcase? Here we go! There are six key features of this T-shirt. Six! Let me sell it to you.
Number one, the logo on the front matches the one on the back. Number two, there are stripes on the sleeves to make it to make it really cool.
Number one, the logo on the front matches the one on the back. Number two, there are stripes on the sleeves to make it really cool.
Number three, there are slits along the side to make it breathable and airable.
Number three, there are slits along the sides to make it breathable and airy.
Number four, there are little, little, uh, distressed details on the collar because I got hungry and I decided to nibble a little bit.
Number four, there are little distressed details on the collar because I got hungry and decided to nibble a bit.
Number five, there's a, uh, there's a classic rat logo inside for you.
Number five, there's a classic rat logo inside for you.
Number six, I designed this myself. And yeah, oh, seven actually, there's a really cool, really cool design. Yeah.
Number six, I designed this myself. And oh, seven actually, there's a really cool design. Yeah.
ま、一応日本語も少しあの、グッズの紹介だと思うととてもかっこいいです。是非買ってください。
Well, just a little Japanese introduction for the merch—it's really cool. Please check it out!
Please! Please buy it, it looks so cool, kakaii desho?
Please! Please buy it, it looks so cool, right?
そして、韓国語と...するよ。もしそうよ。
And... let's do it in Korean too. If you say so!
And the second announcement is that on October 9th, CouncilRys will be having their, their—who's there?—our 3D collab stream!
And the second announcement is that on October 9th, CouncilRys will be having our 3D collab stream!
There'll be a lot of singing, games, and s'gon' be a lot of fun. So, have you guys come and watch that as well!
There'll be a lot of singing, games, and it's going to be a lot of fun. So I hope you guys come and watch that as well!
Well, all right guys. I feel like that's it. Kore de shuryo? Owari? Is that, is that it?
Well, alright guys. I feel like that's it. Is that it? Is that the end?
Oh, I wonder. I don't know, they're telling me to go off stage. What? Oh, is it? Oh, no, what? Oh, we're going, that's it!
Oh, I wonder. They're telling me to go off stage. What? Oh, is it? Oh, we're going, that's it!
We're going now! Bye-bye, I had so much fun! I had so much fun. I'll see, I'll see you in the next, I'll see you later.
We're going now! Bye-bye, I had so much fun! I had so much fun. I'll see you in the next stream!
Okay, I'm coming! Bye-bye! Mr. Squeakers, come on, we got to go. We got to go. We got to go. We got to go.
Okay, I'm coming! Bye-bye! Mr. Squeakers, come on, we gotta go. We gotta go!
アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
ウォー！アンコール！ウォー！
Whoa! Encore! Whoa!
完全に予想してなかった en:
Totally didn't expect this,
っていってもしょうがないよね？
I mean, oh well, right?
アンコールもう一曲やるけど
I guess we have time for one more encore song,
アンコールに入る前に
but before we head into the encore,
みんなに言いたかった en:
I just wanted to say...
本当にありがとうございました
Thank you guys so much!
スタッフさん本当にありがとうございます
Thank you to the staff!
そして、私のバックダンサーも
And also to my backup dancers!
アンコール、もし知ってたら
For the encore, if you know it,
一つの可能な歌
there's only one song we can do!
ヒーロー！！
Hero!!
ONE PUNCH!
(Three! Two! One! Kill shot!)
参上！必勝！至上最強！！
Appearing! Certain victory! The supreme strongest!!
なんだってんだ? フラストレーション 僕は止まらない
What're ya saying? Frustration. I won't stop.
ONE PUNCH! 完遂! 連戦連勝!
ONE PUNCH! Complete! A succession of victories!
僕は喝!! 常に勝つ!! 圧勝!!
I shout out!! I always win!! Complete victory!!
Power! Get power! ギリギリ限界まで
Power! Get power! To the limit!
HERO 俺を讃える声や 喝采なんて 欲しくはないさ
Hero, I don't want voices praising me or acclamation.
HERO だから 人知れず 悪と闘う
Hero, that's why I fight evil in secret.
(Nobody knows who he is.)
天(そら)覆い 押し寄せる敵 俺は背中は向けはしない
Enemies closing in, covering the sky, I won't turn my back on them.
HERO ならば 揺るぎなき覚悟したため 繰り出せ鉄拳
If I'm a hero, then I've prepared unwavering resolve, so I'll unleash my fists.
(Three! Two! One! Fight back!)
参上! Go on! 正々堂々!!
Appearing! Go on! Fair and square!!
どうなってんだ? なにも感じねぇ もはや敵居ねぇー!
What's happening? I don't feel anything. My enemies are gone now!
JUSTICE! 執行! 問答無用!
Justice! Enforcement! No use arguing about it!
俺が断つ!! 悪を断つ!! 合掌!!
I'll cut it off!! Cut off evil!! Hands together in prayer!!
Power! Get power! アドレナリン溢れ出すぜ!
Power! Get power! Adrenaline's overflowing!
Power! Get power! 鍛えた技をぶちかませ!
Power! Get power! Strike hard with tempered technique!
HERO どんなに 強い奴も ちっぽけなガキだったんだ
Hero, no matter how strong the enemy, they used to be tiny brats.
HERO 弱き 己乗り越え 強くなる
Hero, I overcome my weak self and get stronger.
(Nobody knows who he is.)
神宿る 拳掲げて 俺は突き進むだけさ
Raising fists with gods dwelling in them, I'll just plunge forward.
HERO いつか 敗北に泥塗まれるまで 戦うHERO
Hero, until someday I taste the dirt in defeat, a fighting hero.
俺は諦めない その胸に未来(あす)を描き
I won't give up. I picture the future in that heart.
目覚め行く 世界へ今 舞い上がれ 強く高く
Soar up into the awakening world now, stronger, higher.
どんな時でも なにがあっても
No matter what, no matter what happens...
HERO 俺を讃える声や 喝采なんて 欲しくはないさ
Hero, I don't want voices praising me or acclamation.
HERO だから 人知れず 悪と闘う
Hero, that's why I fight evil in secret.
(Nobody knows who he is.)
神宿る 拳掲げて 俺は突き進むだけさ
Raising fists with gods dwelling in them, I'll just plunge forward.
HERO いつか 敗北に泥塗まれるまで 戦うHERO
Hero, until someday I taste the dirt in defeat, a fighting hero.
孤独なHERO
A lonely hero...
I wanna be 最強HERO!
I wanna be the strongest hero!
HERO 俺を讃える声や 喝采なんて 欲しくはないさ
Hero, I don't want voices praising me or acclamation.
HERO だから 人知れず 悪と闘う
Hero, that's why I fight evil in secret.
(Nobody knows who he is.)
神宿る 拳掲げて 俺は突き進むだけさ
Raising fists with gods dwelling in them, I'll just plunge forward.
HERO いつか 敗北に泥塗まれるまで 戦うHERO
Hero, until someday I taste the dirt in defeat, a fighting hero.
孤独なHERO
A lonely hero...
I wanna be 最強HERO!
I wanna be the strongest hero!
Thank you everyone!
I'll see you next time!
バイバイ！ありがとう！
Bye-bye! Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
This 3D showcase was only possible because of you guys,
so from the bottom of my heart thank you.
I love you guys so much!